Becky Sable

UX Designer & Researcher



rebsable@gmail.com

9 412-478-0757

Pittsburgh

bsabledesigns.github.io



Hello, I am a UX designer, who is passionate about all things UX. My eight years of relevant work experience, combined with intuitive skills, such as excellent problem solving abilities and an innate understanding of human interactions along with research skills brought me to the UX? field.

EDUCATION

UX/UI Design CertificateBoulder Digital Arts

M.S. Mediterranean Studies University of Malta M.A. Conflict Analysis & Resolution George Mason University

B.A. Afro-American Studies
George Mason University

EXPERIENCE

UX Designer

ADP

2017 - Present

Research and identify problems through stakeholders and user research in complex industry of HR software. Design and validate workflows and interfaces through interactions. Collaborate with multiple roles to drive alignments.

UX Designer

Freelancer

2014 - 2017

Conducted user and market research, created user personas, user flows, sketches, wireframes, and prototypes for responsive websites and mobile apps.

Event Coordinator

Jewish Federation of Pittsburgh 2014

Planned, coordinated, and executed 20+ events per year with up to 2,000 attendees per event. Oversaw team of vendors and managed contracts and deadlines.

Program Coordinator

University of Pittsburgh

2013

Researched and developed online learning module for PA Prepared Learning Management system. Collaborated with local organizations and experts to create effective learning tool.

Account Manager / Sales Rep

Istanblu

2009-2010

Created clientele portfolio by representing product to prospective buyers. Developed plans to increase revenue and maintained second highest sale performance within company.

Assistant to Senior Vice President

Prudential Realty

2008-2009

Provided executive-level support with a demonstrated ability to improvise, improve procedures, and meet demanding deadlines.

DESIGN SKILLS

Mobile design Interaction design Prototype design Web design

ALL THINGS UX

Organizer of UX Happy Hour in Pittsburgh Co-organizer of IxDA Pittsburgh Creator of UX Pgh slack channel

TOOLS I USE

Sketch InVision Photoshop HTML/CSS Mac OS X